(Girl:)Curious George is a monkey.
(Sheldon:)Somewhat anthropomorphized, but yes.
(Sheldon:)Say...
(Sheldon:)...maybe sometime you and I
could go see monkeys together.
(Sheldon:)- Would you like that?
- Okay.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, what are you doing?
(Sheldon:)I'm making friends with this little girl.
(Sheldon:)- What's your name?
- Rebecca.
(Sheldon:)Hi, Rebecca.
I'm your new friend, Sheldon.
- No, you're not. Let's go.
- I...
(Sheldon:)We were really hitting it off.
(Leonard:)Don't look up, there's cameras.
I'm curious, in the "How Well Do
You Know Sheldon?" section...
...what did you put
for his favorite amino acid?
(Leonard and Howard:)Lysine.
(Raj:)Damn it, I had lysine and changed it.
Oh, good. You're just in time.
(Sheldon:)I believe I've isolated the algorithm
for making friends.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, there is no algorithm
Hear him out. If he's onto something,
we could open a booth at Comic-Con...
(Howard:)...make a fortune.